Hello hello welcome back friends, we heartily welcome you all once
again by
subscribing to our channel friends today we will
talk about the result the result please like
and that subscribe matters
friends subscribe
we will talk about ICICI Bank today's result
friends you can see this bank sinking
and we will also talk a little about it in the financial market
and friends
what you should do in the long term
we will tell you so friends let's start
before starting the video let me
tell you that if you are new to this channel then
please like and subscribe the channel so
that you get daily updates friends
if you
look at the chart then the
price of the bank share is 382 option
friends this bank had picked up a lot
but here on Friday on the
bank side there was a big fall in the bank nifty
so this bank also
fell in it again if we look at the six months here then
friends in 6 months this company had
almost gone close to 290 here you can see
this company had made a
good recovery from there  So, I have just
told you friends, but
if you look at the Friday market, it was 3801, the
hand was 38.72 and the iron was 372, friends, so
you saw a lot of movement
in the Friday market, friends, anyway, if you
look at it, the overall chart of Bank Nifty is
quite good, for this, the
decline in Bank Nifty is quite a
big decline, because
its volume here is
not created well and there is a lot of
business in one lesson, let's
start this video, let's see
how the result of this cotton came, so look here, it is
about 300 crores, here
we see, their profit
percentage cotton, more things are getting good results,
see this
posted here and you subscribe here, but
friends, you think what does this number have to do with it, the
second number is a very useful
thing, and in such a situation, you might not be able to see it from your number,
and you should
definitely look at it and you should find out what this number means, you should
know everything so that
you can make a profit in the long term  You can earn a good amount of money
friends, if we look here then the
net profit is friends,
if we look at the net profit then it is approximately 24
points 8061 of zero percent and
in the quarter, Tronica City 9.20 organization was
told to turn hotspot of friends
in the bank, which is very good thing,
in this situation also if we watch this video then it is
exactly 960 that last year
4520 subscribe there, you
can see here that there is an increase in it,
if we look at it then 60 3.31 is incomplete,
you can see here, if you
look at Google maintained depression over, then 34
point phase that last year 6.30, there also
you are seeing it close to double, we are seeing it even above double, the
graph which sends NPA to
clamps from non-performing assets, friends if you
write that York wardrobe then
we are seeing an increase here, the net NPA which is
also we can see is 6 crores
that gross MP if  Now if we look at 5.46 600
800, we are seeing that the cross NPA is low here
and the
quarterly reduction of 5.5 30 is a very good thing
and if we look at the net NPA, it is 1.23,
we are seeing a decrease in that too, almost
1.70, if we look at the return on that, it
is 0.95 versus its previous, that is, there
also we are seeing a good increase,
0.5 and for not wrong quarter, if we
look at the capital adequacy ratio, then it is
16.12 as compared to the previous quarter, that is, 16.51
quarter, friends, the result overall is very
tremendous, there has been a decrease in Enfield, this is a
very good thing, G.A. The
medicinal qualities of burning of fight
are stronger than that, this is a matter of concern, during the
last seen total provisioning is stronger
than 280, provisioning matters a lot, which
means Sky's appointment can go, if
this can become soft then this
money is not with them.  It may take a long time for the money to come,
which Yudhishthir,
even after doing all that, the full amount was not there, so
you know that this is a
matter of great concern for the youth, the result is
very good,
if we look at this business then the interest and
less interest expanded, you can see here,
we have trended from jun30 Bluetooth
19.95 to z9 corporation,
here these people have
Fifth 120 Bank Made and Additional Kabir
Special, which I have told you,
due to which their entry has
increased a lot, friends,
if you look at the total deposits in the bank and there has been an increase of 21.1,
you can see
it directly, if you look at it, then the
second 41.1 percent here
in the total deposits is huge, here the
balance sheet is increasing very very well, if you had
appointed in that
subscribe 1.5 ICICI
Prudential Life and Profit Subscribe
Sure Subscribe a lot
Subscribe about them here, the result is very
good here and friends, here
we have faltered a little in subscribing,
from there you can see that the appointed is very
excellent, if any big
subscribe, the management is very tremendous,
as you can say it,
friends, here we finally run in
interest and now you can see the net
profit, soon you will see a little
here the operating profit has decreased from June 2017 to
March,
in NPS, here you can see that there is a
decline in net NPA, there is a
decline in gross NPA savings, which is a good
thing, the share holding pattern has been appointed,
subscribe a little more and
buy shares, subscribe here, friends, let's
talk about support,
friends, subscribe three more
friends, here you will get a good amount of subscription, it can give you
very good
returns, it can give you double-triple returns,
upwards I will now
save the screen, if you
take a little bit of result, if you are getting this
subscription, you will be getting  So please don't run away after making a profit
and if you should subscribe
then we will definitely tell you but
friends please subscribe because if
you don't read then we here friends subscribe
here
after that it started falling so you
can see on 24th March it had placed a low of 268 so
whoever bought it here here made a
very good profit for them but whoever invested
here in December-January
friends please subscribe to it
and if you keep it folded then the
ignorance will be destroyed then the
market will fall drastically here and you can suffer a huge
loss so we will
tell you that if you are getting profit then
subscribe and resubscribe, there is no
shortage in the bank, it is a very
good bank but what is going on in the market right now,
hence the
news that has come between China, the
Reserve Bank has said that there can be a
huge financial crisis here,
you can see a lot of them there, they have
shown red signal there, they told
that the pension system is very  It has increased a lot
and he may face more pressure, so
if you have not seen it then if you see the
video in the newspaper then please tell us, we will
tell you that Reserve Bank of India
and if you liked this video then
please like and subscribe to the channel,
thank you.